

MARCIN WRZOŚ

FRONTEND DEVELOPER PORTFOLIO

PROFILE

I am a skilled Front-End Developer with a strong background as a Technical Lead in the corporate sector and over five years of experience within the financial industry. My career blends indepth software development knowledge with excellent interpersonal and leadership abilities, allowing me to drive collaboration and lead cross-functional teams effectively Currently, at Exa22, I design, build and test cloud-based telemetry system that connect machines with a web-based portal.

My expertise lies in React.js, including Hooks and Redux, Typescript and Jest, designing and maintaining interfaces for vending machines such as "Kwiatomaty". I work closely with back-end developers to define API endpoints and application flow while also integrating front-end applications with AWS services, particularly AWS S3 for image retrieval.

HOW TO REACH ME

Phone: +48 662 623 531
Email: marcin.wrzs@gmail.com
Github: github.com/Marcinwrzs
Linkedin: in/marcin-wrzoś/

TECH STACK

React, Hooks/Redux, TypeScript, JavaScript, JEST library, MobX, AWS, GIT, CSS with preprocesor SASS, MUI

EDUCATION

Reskilled

Programming mentorship - work with senior developers on non commercial project in React + Typescript 2023 - 2024

Wrocław University of Economics

Master of Finance and Accounting 2017 - 2019

University of Wrocław

Bachelor of National Security 2014 - 2017

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front end developer

Exa22 | February 2024 to present

- designed and developed cloud-based telemetry systems that connect machines to a web-based portal in React with Typescript
- · wrote tests for front-end applications using Jest
- designed and maintained interfaces for vending machines such as "Kwiatomaty" using React.js
- integrated front-end applications with AWS services, utilizing Amazon S3 for image retrieval
- collaborated closely with back-end developers to define API endpoints and application flow

Technical Lead, Broker Accreditation Analyst

Axa XL | January 2023 to present

- process automation in VBA and low-code applications
- · coordinating process improvement initiatives
- run the meetings and presenting solutions to the team

Non-it jobs in financial industry

January 2018 - January 2023

PROJECTS

Foodie

View code and demo

Tech Stack: React, Typescript, react-router, Context API, ReactSlick.

Foodie is a versatile application that communicate via http with the external Api spoonacular, offering a rich repository of recipes. Seamlessly integrated with a secure backend server for user registration and authentication, Foodie allows users to discover popular recipes and rate them, search by category or name, view detailed recipe information, and build a collection of favorites.

Portfolio

View code

Tech Stack: React, Typescript, MUI.

Introducing a resume application that shows my skills and professional achievement.

Memory game

View code

Tech Stack: React, Typescript, MobX.

The project is an implementation of a Memory game using React, TypeScript, and MobX